4reesoft.com 2014-02-14

# download from 4reesoft.com Privacy Policy

### Your Acceptance

This privacy policy ("Policy") explains how personally identifiable information is collected, used and disclosed by (4reeSoft) with respect to your access and use of 4reeSofts online file storage and sharing service located at [www.4reeSoft.com ](http://www.4reesoft.com/home.php) (the "Service") 4reeSoft Photo, 4reeSoft Music and 4reeSoft ("Apps" or "App"), so you can make an informed decision about using the Service.

We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on this Policy the date it was last updated. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to review this Policy from time-to-time to make sure that you understand how any personally identifiable information you provide to us or collected about you will be used.

4reeSoft.has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@4reeSoft.com](mailto:support@4reeSoft.com)

### What Is Personal Information?

As used in this Policy, the term "personally identifiable information" means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, user name or e-mail address), or information about that individual that is directly linked to information that specifically identifies an individual. Personally identifiable information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of the Service or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities or other personally identifiable information has been removed. This Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information.

### What Information Do We Collect?

**Active Collection:** We collect information from you in various ways when you use the Service and Apps. For example, we collect information: (i) that you voluntarily provide to us (such as when you send us an email); and (ii) to which you provide us access. Such information may include personal information, such as your name, email address, date of birth, social network data and performance related data. When using our Apps we will collect information such as device type, operating system type and version. Personal and demographic information may also be collected if you provide such information in connection with posting data, providing access to your online groups and other activities in connection with the Service.

We do not ask you for, access or track any location based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our Mobile Apps or services.

Passive Collection: Passive Collection: When you use the Service and our Apps, some information is also automatically collected, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring website, and your activity on the Service. We may also automatically collect certain logistical information in server logs, including information about how you use various features of the Service and information about the number, frequency and length of each session.

We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies" when you use the Service. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive at the request of a website. Among other things, cookies help us to improve the Service and your experience. If we link cookies to any personally identifiable information, we will treat this information as personally identifiable information. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser manufacturer to learn about these functions. However, if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services made available via the Service.

The use of cookies by our partners is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

We may use Web beacons or similar technology on the Service and in our Apps. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. Web beacons are small, invisible graphic images that may be used on the Service or in emails relating to the Service to collect certain information and monitor user activity on the Service, such as to count visits, understand usage effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon. Such technologies are used to collect aggregate statistics related to usage of the Service and do not collect personally identifiable information

Personally identifiable information will be stored on secured servers,and we may store and process personally identifiable information in the United States and other countries.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

www.4reesoft.com collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
\- To improve our Site  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
\- To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### How Do We Use the Personally Identifiable Information We Collect?

We use personally identifiable information collected through the Service and Apps for the purposes described in this Policy or elsewhere on the Service or in the Apps. For example, we may use personally identifiable information we collect:

  * To process and complete any transactions in connection with the Service and Apps.
  * To request feedback and to otherwise contact you about your use of the Service and Apps.
  * To respond to your emails, questions, comments, requests and complaints, and to provide customer service. 
  * To monitor and analyze Service and App usage and trends.
  * To personalize and improve the Service or Apps, and our users' experiences with the Service and Apps (such as providing content or features that match interests), and to increase the Service's or Apps’ functionality and user friendliness.
  * To send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, additional information about our products and services and support and administrative messages, and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Service or Apps. When sending marketing information about our services or products, we will only use your email address used during registration; we will not use other email addresses you may have provided to us, for instance in a feedback form, to send marketing emails.
  * To notify you about important changes to the Service and Apps.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

f your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or delete it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support@4reeSoft.com](mailto:support@4reeSoft.com) We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

If you wish to request the deletion of an unauthorized profile you may contact us at [support@4reeSoft.com](mailto:support@4reeSoft.com)

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Links to Other Websites

The Service may contain links to other websites. Any personally identifiable information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third- party and is subject to that third- party's privacy policy. This Policy does not apply to such linked websites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these websites or any other websites that are linked to/from the Service. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personally identifiable information.

### What Steps Do We Take To Protect Your Information Online

We take reasonable measures to protect your personally identifiable information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can guarantee against any interception or any other type of misuse. To assist with the protection of personally identifiable information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Service and Apps by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@4reeSoft.com](mailto:support@4reeSoft.com)

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. 

### DMCA (Digital Millennium Copyright Act ) :

This site all the files, software and other resources are reproduced from the forum or blog. If the violation of your copyright, please inform, we will remove within 24 hours. [Contact Us](http://www.4reesoft.com/contact.php)

4reeSoft.com takes copyright violation very seriously and is committed to protecting the rights of copyright owners. 4reeSoft users are bound by the Terms of Use as well as by law to respect authors’ rights. Users may not copy, adapt, distribute, or publicly display or perform works of original authorship without the authorization of the respective rights holders. 

### Notice to Owners of Copyrighted Works

If you are the copyright owner of content which appears on 4reeSoft website and you did not authorize the use of the content you must notify 4reeSoft in writing in order for us to identify the allegedly infringing content and take action.[Contact Us](http://www.4reesoft.com/contact.php)

Your written notice must include the following: 

  * A physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner or authorized person acting on behalf of the owner which expressly claims an executive right that is allegedly being infringed.
  * Specific identification of the copyrighted work which you are alleging to have been infringed. If you are alleging infringement of multiple copyrighted works with a single notification you must submit a representative list which specifically identifies each of the works that you allege are being infringed.
  * Specific identification of the location and description of material that is claimed to be infringing or to be subject of infringing activity with enough detailed information to permit 4reeSoft to locate the material. You should include the specific URL or URLs of the webpages where the allegedly infringing material is located.
  * Information reasonably sufficient to allow 4reeSoft to contact the complaining party which may include a name, address, telephone number and electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted.
  * A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by copyright owner, its agent or the law.
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

copyright infringement claim form at: our copyright infringement claim form

Please also note that any person who knowingly materially misrepresents information in the take-down notification may be subjected to liability, including compensatory damages for all parties harmed by reliance on the misrepresentation.

Allow one business day to respond to your notice and take necessary actions. To ensure proper consideration of your notice, please make sure that you provide all the information outlined in the notification requirements above.

### Counter-notification

4reeSoft.com respects the legitimate interests of copyright owners as well as users. Users are afforded an opportunity to respond to claims of infringement and to obtaining timely restoration of removed material or the user’s access to the website in case of sufficient proof of legitimate use of the removed material.

Users may respond to a copyright infringement claim by submitting a counter-notification. The counter-notification must contain the following information:

  * A statement that access to the user’s account or file was disabled due to operation of a notice and takedown procedure.
  * Information sufficient to identify the material that has been removed, including the account identification information and the URL address where the material could be located prior to removal.
  * A statement under penalty of perjury that the user has a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification.
  * The users name and contact information, including address and telephone number.
  * A statement that the user consents to the jurisdiction of the Federal District Court for the judicial district in which the user’s address is located, or if the user's address is outside of the United States, for any judicial district in which the service provider may be found, and that the user will accept service of process from the person who provided the take-down notification.
  * The user’s electronic or physical signature.

Counter-notification should be submitted to 4reeSoft’s DMCA Designated Agent at the addresses provided in the section above. 4reeSoft will respond to a valid counter-notification in no less than 10 and no more than 14 business days.

### Advertising

We partner with a third party ad network to display advertising within our Apps. Our ad network partner uses Web beacons and log files to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on our Apps to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt- out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

### DoubleClick DART Cookie 

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.4reesoft.com. .:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.4reesoft.com and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense Clickbank

### Facebook Connect

You can log in to our Service (or link your App to your social network) using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

### Twitter Connect

You can log in to our Service (or link your App to your social network) using sign-in services such as Twitter Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Twitter Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Service includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Questions

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [support@4reeSoft.com](mailto:support@4reeSoft.com)

### 

**Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

Changes to this privacy policy

www.4reesoft.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Notification of Changes

4reesoft.com reserves the right to change, update or revise the terms of this Policy, and/or impose new conditions, policies or additional rules. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our web site. Any such changes, together with the remainder of any unaltered version of this Privacy Policy will constitute Lime Wire's Privacy Policy at the time of such notice and will be effective immediately upon posting. Your continued use of the Lime Wire Websites or the Program following posting or notification of any such changes shall serve as your acceptance of these changes and agreement to the revised Privacy Policy.
